

ABOUT

I'm Frontend Developer with more than 2 years of experience specializing in software design and development. I used to work at TMA and AEGONA in a professional environment. I can optimize the software for processing speed to make the user experience better

EDUCATION

HUFLIT (2018 - 2022)

Major: Information Technology Bachelor Degree: Very good

GPA: 8.15



LANGUAGES

English 530 Toeic

Communication intermediate

NGUYỄN KIM TIỀN

MIDDLE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

© 076 355 7366

Go Vap, TP.HCM

tienkim9920@gmail.com

https://tienkim.netlify.app



EXPERIENCE

TMA SOLUTIONS

Time: 2021 - 2022 Fresher Frontend

Developer

AEGONA LTD

Time: 2022 - 2023 Junior Frontend

Developer

EXPERIENCE SKILLS

3+ years of experience in ReactJS

1 years of experience in Angular, VueJS

Analysis Software, Design Pattern,

Organization, Lead Team, Design Software



GENERAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, RESTful API,
Bootstrap, Material UI, Ant Design, Flutter,
NodeJS, Github, Gitlab, Azure Devops